stockpodium.com 2012-06-21

# Security and Privacy Policy | StockPodium

[home](http://www.stockpodium.com/en/) »   Licensing and Policies »   **Security & Privacy**

## Automatically collected personal information

Certain information may be collected automatically when you visit our site. Your IP address, site that reffered you, browser information and also navigation information may be collected to better our service.

We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. Additionally, for systems administration, detecting usage patterns and troubleshooting purposes, our web servers automatically log standard access information including browser type, access times/open mail, URL requested, and referral URL. This information is not shared with third parties and is used only within StockPodium on a need-to-know basis. Any individually identifiable information related to this data will never be used in any way different to that stated above without your explicit permission.

## Personal data provided by you

Upon registration or in your profile pages you are requested to to fill in fields that may contain some personal information - names, address, telephone number, e-mail address, etc. Other additional infromation may be collected to provide you with some service/product or process any licensing transaction.

Private information, collected by StockPodium will be kept as long as needed to justify the purposes of its collection.

The security of your personal information is of great importance to us. Whenever you are asked to share personal information, we use operational functions to secure it. However StockPodium does not warrant that its website is impenetrable or invulnerable to hackers.

The personal data collected by StockPodium are for internal use only and may be used to maintain or update your profile/account, send you updates of our services/products, process orders and issue invoices and optimize the use of our site. Parts of your personal information may be used to conduct credit inquiries.

Client records are regarded as confidential and therefore will not be divulged to any third party, other than content providers, service providers, who perform services on its behalf, necessary payment processors or courier services if legally required to do so to the appropriate authorities. These companies will only obtain the personal information they need to deliver the service and are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose.  
This information may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition or sale of the company and/or its assets.

We will not sell, share, or rent your personal information to any third party or use your e-mail address for unsolicited mail. Any emails sent by StockPodium will only be in connection with the provision of agreed services and products.

## Cookies

We use cookie, that is stored to your computer to beter our sevice, store your preferences and also ensure electronic identifiable information which identifies the user's computer is properly served. You can set your browser's options not to accept cookies, but this may prevent you from accessing some or all of the features of this site.

## Links

Be aware that this website contain links to other sites that are covered by their own privacy policies. StockPodium is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We advice our users to carefully read the privacy statements of each and every website that they are referred to by StockPodium.
